in this lesson I'll walk you through
在这一课中 我将带你一览无余
installing the custom brushes and other
安装自定义画笔和其他
content for my cre a training course
我的履历培训课程的内容
you'll need to download the resource
您需要下载该资源
files from the course page before moving
移动前课程页面中的文件
forward this is a compressed folder that
转发这是一个压缩的文件夹
you'll need to extract using a free
您需要使用免费的
application called szip or by using the
名为sZip的应用程序或使用
extractor built into your operating
您的操作中内置了抽取器
system you can do this by right clicking
系统您可以通过右键单击来执行此操作
on the file once extracted you'll be
在解压后的文件上 您将
able to install the contents you'll be
能够安装您将要安装的内容
installing these files into cre using
使用将这些文件安装到cre中
various methods I will explain what all
各种方法我都会解释一下
of this custom content can do throughout
此自定义内容的
the course let's start with the brushes
这门课让我们从刷子开始
and workspace I'll run cre then open
和工作区我将运行cre 然后打开
settings manage resources and click on
设置管理资源 然后单击
import
进口
resources select the three bundles for
资源选择以下三个捆绑包
brushes brush tips and workspace these
画笔笔尖和工作空间这些
will install my custom brushes and a
将安装我的自定义画笔和一个
custom layout you'll see the brushes
自定义布局您将看到画笔
appear in the brush presets panel there
显示在那里的画笔预设面板中
are also categories or tags you can use
也是您可以使用的类别或标记
to filter out only my brushes
只过滤掉我的画笔
in the top right menu you can choose to
在右上方的菜单中 您可以选择
enable and disable any of the brush
启用和禁用任何画笔
bundles you have installed into cre you
您已安装到cre中的捆绑包
can also go to settings manage resource
还可以转到设置管理资源
library to activate or deactivate
要激活或停用的库
these next we'll activate the custom
接下来 我们将激活该自定义
workspace from the window menu this will
从窗口菜单中选择工作区 这将
arrange the cre UI to match my
安排CRE用户界面以匹配我的
demonstrations the remaining content
演示其余内容
needs to be placed inside of one of
需要放置在其中一个
crea's application folders in the manage
管理中的CREA应用程序文件夹
resources menu click on open resource
资源菜单单击打开资源
folder adding content to this folder is
文件夹将内容添加到此文件夹是
how you get it to show up in CR we'll be
你如何让它出现在CR中我们将是
copying my custom content here but any
将我的自定义内容复制到此处 但不复制
content you have created such as brushes
您创建的内容 如画笔
keyboard shortcuts or preset canvas
键盘快捷键或预设画布
sizes can be found here as well copy the
尺寸也可以在这里找到 复制
custom AR profile to the input folder
自定义AR配置文件到输入文件夹
this will install a custom AR canvas
这将安装一个自定义AR画布
input settings profile which has some
输入设置配置文件 它具有一些
custom keyboard
自定义键盘
shortcuts next copy the entire
快捷键下一步复制整个
predefined image sizes folder to the
预定义的图像大小文件夹复制到
creat a resource folder this this will
这将创建一个资源文件夹
load some predefined canvas sizes you
加载一些预定义的画布大小
can choose from in the new document
可以在新文档中进行选择
menu after that you'll need to close and
菜单之后 您将需要关闭并
reopen CR to get it to recognize the
重新打开CR以使其识别
files you added next in window configure
您在窗口配置中添加的下一个文件
Crea choose the custom AR canvas input
CREA选择自定义AR画布输入
settings profile then in keyboard
然后在键盘中设置配置文件
shortcuts choose the custom AR profile
快捷方式选择自定义AR配置文件
this is a set of more keyboard shortcuts
这是一组更多的键盘快捷键
once you are finished you should now
一旦你完成了 你现在就应该
have a workspace that very closely
拥有一个非常接近的工作空间
matches the one I am using in my course
与我在课程中使用的相匹配
rather than install everything from my
而不是从我的
workspace if you'd like to extract any
工作区 如果您要提取任何
of the individual brushes or files from
来自的单个画笔或文件的
my bundles simply duplicate the bundle
我的捆绑包简单地复制了捆绑包
file and rename it to a zip file this
文件 并将其重命名为压缩文件
will allow you to see the custom content
将允许您查看自定义内容
within a bundle the paint op presets
在捆绑包内的绘制操作预设
folder is where you'll find the brushes
文件夹是你可以找到画笔的地方
copy these to the same folder in the
将这些文件复制到
creat a resource
创建资源
Library it's important to note that you
库需要注意的是 您
need to use underscores rather than
需要使用下划线而不是
spaces in the file names of your brushes
画笔文件名中的空格
otherwise they may not be detected by
否则 它们可能不会被
crto when you import them simply rename
导入时只需重命名即可
the files in the file explorer if you
文件资源管理器中的文件 如果
need to there may also be brush tips you
需要的话也可能有刷子提示你
need to copy over to the corresponding
需要复制到相应的
brushes
刷子
folder close and reopen cre to apply
关闭并重新打开要应用的cre文件夹
those changes the new brushes will
新画笔将会有这些变化
appear in your local Resources directory
显示在您的本地资源目录中
in the manage resources menu
在管理资源菜单中
alternatively you can copy the brushes
或者 您也可以复制画笔
you want to a folder and then choose
您想要一个文件夹 然后选择
import resources from the manage
从管理器导入资源
resources
资源
menu if you want to make a custom bundle
菜单 如果您想要定制捆绑包
of my brushes grouped together with your
我的画笔和你的画笔组合在一起
own custom brushes then you'll need to
拥有定制的画笔 那么您将需要
copy all of the brushes you want to
复制您想要的所有画笔
bundle to the local Resources
捆绑到本地资源
directory you may need to add tags to
您可能需要向其中添加标记的目录
the brushes if you want to sort them
画笔 如果您想要对它们进行排序
into
vt.进入 进入
groups it will be easier to make the
群组将更容易使
bundle if you deactivate some of the
捆绑包如果您停用某些
other unwanted brush bundles
其他不需要的刷子束
first choose create a bundle and select
首先选择创建捆绑包并选择
all of the brushes you want to package
您想要包装的所有画笔
together click on the arrows to move the
一起单击箭头以移动
brushes from the Creed application on
Creed应用程序中的画笔
the left to the new bundle on on the
左到新捆绑上
right be sure to enable embed tags to
正确的 请务必启用嵌入标签
save those with the bundle as
保存那些拥有捆绑包的人作为
well after that close C and delete the
之后关闭C并删除
brushes from the local resources library
来自本地资源库的画笔
to prevent
防止
duplicates next reopen cre and import
重复下次重新开放cre和进口
your newly created bundle from the
您从
manage resources
管理资源
menu you may need to deactivate then
然后您可能需要停用菜单
reactivate the new bundle to get the
重新激活新捆绑包以获取
tags to work properly now you have
标签现在可以正常工作了
merged my custom brushes with your own I
将我的自定义画笔与您自己的I合并
recommend going going into the cre a
建议进入cre a
resource library and backing up your
资源库并备份您的
bundle in case you ever need to
捆绑 以防万一
reinstall
重新安装
it
它